contact us: turkision@gmail.com
Yakup Bey,sent his daughter to Konya
for a reason.
He wants to declare his own sultanate
and take oaths of loyalty.
Then the seal...
He will use it to gather the beys behind him.
Maybe a document to promote his sultanate...
Son, go to Yenisehir and
tell your father what's going on.
Let Osman Bey ruin their plans.
Let me kiss, mother.
Have a safe journey, Alaaddin Ali.
Thanks, mother. Thanks.
Food!
Master Vasillis. I knew it.
Osman Bey, why are you so furious?
Who are you comparing me with?
How dare you standing against me?
I'm neither Vizier Alemshah who you beheaded...
...nor Ismihan Hatun who you sent to exile.
I'm not here to gain power.
My power is already beyond everybody.
My homeland is already prosperous.
I came to put the frontiers in order.
I was already a sultan.
My sultanate is just stating the obvious.
Answer my question.
But while answering
...take a warning from the names you counted.
I only take lessons, not warnings.
They tolerated you too much, obviously.
I won't.
Why are you holding a dagger then?
If I had a dagger, I wouldn't hide it.
I was hiding your mistake.
What mistake? What mistake would I even make?
It was the dagger of the person
who attempted to kill me, Osman Bey.
I thought you were on my side.
I never thought you would ambush me.
But you didn't think we were allies.
And now you are slandering?
What game are you talking about?
Here is the proof! If there are any slanders,
it's you who are casting them.
Who knows with which heathen’s words
you are calling me to account?
You can't fool me.
But you are already fooled.
You brought it to use as a leverage.
And now you are even talking about a game?
Before you accuse someone,
clean the dirt on your hands first.
Maybe, the dirt came one me when
you tried to make me kiss your hand.
Oh no, Beys! People expect unity from us.
This is not a good time.
Stop this.
It wouldn't suit you, Beys.
You are pioneers. Don't do this.
This wouldn't end up well.
You'll come to the opening of the market
and correct your mistake.
My sultanate will spread to the whole land.
You will come and pledge loyalty.
We are leaving!
You can't just say your words and then leave!
What is this supposed to mean, Osman Bey?
Like Beys said,
...people shouldn't think we are at odds.
Let me walk to the yard with you.
Alright then. See you
in the market tomorrow, hatuns.
Malhun Hatun, you should come
and see your stall too.
Everybody's stall is ready.
If you're late, you remain hungry.
I will come Saadet Hatun.
Don't worry.
I care about my people, of course.
Princess Holofira, I'd like to host you
in my market before you leave.
Obviously, you are good at trading.
Holofira must have other things to do.
Another time, if Allah permits.
Does the lady not have a tongue,
Malhun Hatun?
I will definitely come by
before I leave, Saadet Hatun.
I got a nice stall prepared
in the market for the Kayi rugs.
Coins will fill in your pouches.
Holofira go to my room and wait for me.
My mother doesn't like someone talking
over her words, Holofira.
Go there now.
Only a cup.
Another cup.
-Your captivity is over, Remus.
-Thank God.
You'll get out of the palace. But first,
Master Vasillis has another mission for you.
Did you get hosted well, Saadet Hatun?
Thankfully, Malhun Hatun
provided everything for us.
-Thank you, Osman Bey.
-Thank you, thank you.
Tonight your tranquility protected you, Osman Bey.
Don't count on my tranquility too much!
It may be overwhelmed by my wrath any time.
If you get overwhelmed by your wrath,
you will be a loser forever.
Stay safe.
Osman Bey!
Just pledge loyalty.
I'm both older and more powerful than you.
Stop being arrogant so we both will be safe.
Those fighting for Allah never get arrogant!
I hope your cause of fight is always
to spread Allah's words! Stay safe!
Why did we stop, my Bey?
What happened, Osman?
Someone tried to assassinate Yakup Bey.
And the one who tried to assassinate
him had this Kayi's dagger.
Hatuns' table was not peaceful either.
Apparently, there will be discomfort.
I think it is a game, my Bey.
If he had this before, he would use it.
He took it out when he was in trouble.
We should've handled it when we had him.
Knowing where to stop is better than
making a move, my son
Konur arrived just in time.
Yakup Bey's son Mehmet surrounded
Yenisehir with an army.
They have no fear.
I should go and check Holofira.
If they shed any blood, the peace and union
in Yenisehir would disappear.
-What about our reputation, my Bey?
-Orhan!
What if we shed blood at dinner? What would happen then?
Would our reputation be in its place?
We know this... but what about people?
How could our people support us?
Start a fire.
It will be a long night.
These roads are not safe
for a girl like you, Holofira.
This place is nothing like
the place you came from.
I can protect myself, I assure you.
We saw how you protected yourself.
If it wasn't your son Orhan who faced my dagger...
...those bandits could not have taken me,
Malhun Hatun.
Choose your words wisely
when talking about Orhan Bey.
Do not forget he is a Shahzade, Princess Holofira.
I’m sorry, but no one has the right
to tell me what to do in this palace.
If you are our guest here, you will obey my rules.
You won't talk to Saadet Hatun during your visit.
You won't go to the frontiers marketplace.
But... as you said... I am a guest, not a slave.
And I will not live by following someone's rules.
That's not how I was raised.
What are you doing, sister?
Brother.. You scared me.
What are you doing here?
Don't even ask.
My mother is questioning Holofira.
Apparently she will send Holofira, brother.
Why? Did something happen at the table?
-I should tell you.
Forget Holofira.
Can I come in, mother?
Orhan! Get ready.
You will take her to her land as soon as possible.
Holofira!
Holofira! Wait.
-What do you want, Orhan?
-What did my mother tell you?
She is expecting me to obey your rules.
But tell her, I am never going to follow your rules.
Calm down.
My mother is not doing that
because she has bad intentions.
I know. I know.
We both want the same thing.
My farewell.
So? When am I leaving?
Holofira...
Go to your room. I will go to my father
and come back. We will talk.
Walk! Walk!
-Let me go!
-Come on! Walk!
My Shahzade...
He was hiding in a corner and writing this.
Yakup Bey's son Mehmet Bey...
...took Sogut's inn for himself.
Boran Bey must be informed.
Didn't I tell you that
no news will be sent to Yenisehir?
You did, my Bey!
-Who made you write this?
-My Bey, I wrote it!
Take him and make him speak.
Let's see how many spies we have among us.
Swords will not be put back to their sheathes
until the sun rises!
-All Alps will be on alert!
-Yes my Shahzade!
Attention!
I prepared everything in advance,
I thought we would stay here.
-They are all from Germiyan.
-You thought well.
You became a mountain behind us.
Thank you Mehmed.
If Osman Bey made a move,
this mountain would crash him.
What is his intention, my Bey?
He can't have invited you for dinner.
He is trying to take revenge for his reputation
which I destroyed.
He will not let it go.
Osman has Remus.
Remus...
It leads to the palace's yard. Osman is there.
Come, Remus. Come.
You know what happened between
us and Yakup Bey. But...
...if he is telling the truth, if Remus is working for
the infidels and working with crusaders...
There is nothing impossible, my Bey.
We've witnessed many games.
Therefore, we will be careful.
We will think about this before we make a move.
We will keep making our moves about Yakup Bey.
We will not stop.
-What are we going to do, my Bey?
-First..
...We will not let them surround Yenisehir
like that again.
Our patrol Alps will also be careful
about the other Alps outside.
My Bey... I think what we should do is obvious.
Now this issue has turned into a reputation issue.
My Bey. How do people know you in this land?
Aren't you the head of Ghazis?
Let's fight, my Bey. Let's conquer lands!
You said 'Let Germiyan protect us'
when we made this decision.
-Why do you want to fight now, Bayindir Bey?
-Orhan Bey...
Our Bey asked, and we explained our opinion.
We chose our way years ago...
Our way...
...is the way of conquest behind our Bey.
Thank you. That's what suits us.
Let them play their games, we will move forward.
We will! But Yakup Bey knew
what was going to happen to him.
He surrounded the city and then came here.
He knew we had Remus.
If he didn't have Remus...
He wouldn't be able find the courage
to sit on the table with sword.
-What do you mean he came with sword?
-Mehmed, hold on.
It's not the time to stop. You said he has Remus.
What are we going to do if he makes him talk?
-I’ll break Yenisehir down.
-Mehmed!
Listen to me my Bey!
He already talked to Remus,
seeing that he confronted us.
But his power was not enough for this.
Son, if we kill Osman...
...we will have to deal with...
...Akinji and Gaziyan.
Our Sultanate...
...wouldn't be in legitimate terms.
First of all,
...we will ruin his reputation
little by little.
So that his people will come one by one...
...and stand behind us.
Osman will make conquests
to boost his reputation.
To where?
Yakup Bey has surrounded as all around.
He is ruining our reputation,
trying to break down our walls.
But we will break
his siege with conquests.
To where, my Bey?
-Let's move towards Kestel.
-Right.
We were preparing for Kestel
siege and we ceased it.
We will start right away,
with Allah's permission.
No.
We will not move towards Kestel.
What's your order, my Bey?
We will go to the place...
...where evil started and
they ruined our reputation,
...we will go to Lefke.
We will punish those who did this to us.
This is a challenge for sultanship.
There's no turning back.
Osman was preparing to move towards
Kestel before Sultan died.
Not Kestel...
...he will go to the castle
where he lost his reputation,
-To Lefke.
-Are we going to let him do that, my Bey?
Of course we will not.
-Kanyumaz
-Yes, my Sultan.
Go to the tribe Beys under the rule of Kayis.
No one will reinforce Alps to Osman.
I'll deem them as my enemy if they do so.
-Let them know.
-Yes, my Sultan.
Osman will try to do everything
to save his reputation.
I'll be against hem at his every move.
He wouldn't do it just for his reputation.
Osman’s real purpose is not to obey.
A flock with two shepherds
will either attack each other...
...or jackals hunt them down.
My people do not deserve this.
Osman is being persistent about it.
If he does not obey...
...I'll destroy his palace.
Tomorrow will be a long day.
Come on.
Osman Bey!
-Remus?
-My Bey, he escaped the dungeon.
And when I saw the arrow...
How did this happen?
No one but Veysel saw him.
Aren't you their leader? Answer me!
They are trying to kill me in our own palace!
We're trying to save and fix our reputation!
-It will not happen again my Bey.
-It will not happen again! Look at me!
You'll find out who did this.
If there's a spy inside,
you'll find out each one of them.
Go away!
Give his reward.
It was a great move. You'll be rewarded
either with coin or position.
Holofira.
Are you asleep?
Very well, I'm leaving then.
I know you're there.
Look, I have an important news for you.
But I guess you're not curious
as you're not answering the door!
Very well, I’m leaving then.
What's that? What will you say?
I'm talking to you.
What's that important thing?
Did my mother upset you?
Was that the important thing?
Very important.
Is there anything more important than this?
-You liar.
-Holofira, wait.
Holofira, tell me.
You were not upset, were you?
Look, my mother talks harshly, but...
-...actually...
-No one can upset me, Shahzade.
Your mother does not know me yet.
Actually, you know what?
You don't know me either.
And that's the issue.
I’m not a dove you can put in a cage.
I'm not a slave who would do everything I'm told to do.
I'm Holofira.
I will not stay here for long.
Make preparations, Shahzade Orhan.
You can't be a dove anyway.
You have claws, daughter of the Lord.
My Osman, table is ready.
Thank you Malhun, thank you.
However, I do not want it right now.
Osman, I have to tell you something.
You have to talk with Orhan.
He is in love with Holofira, but it can not happen.
You have to convince him.
Holofira is not muslim.
Why are you saying this?
What if she becomes a muslim?
I hope so, I hope it happens
the way you say, but I know what I see.
The girl is fanatic Christian.
Wears a cross up to her feet.
So you're saying there's no chance?
That is not the only matter.
She grew up comfortably. Knows no boundaries.
I say we find a good
Turkmen girl for Orhan.
Don't get me involved in this.
You can figure this out with Orhan.
-What will happen then, if you don't say anything?
-I am heading to conquest.
The rest is yours. Now tell me,
are the goods ready to go to bazaar?
They are ready.
Saadet Hatun is probably waiting for us.
Their intentions is to stomp us.
Do not ever kneel to Saadet Hatun.
stay so strong in that bazaar that,
make it unbearable for them.
-So that they understand they can't hurt us.
-Do not worry, she doesn't know me yet.
Then, introduce yourself to me.
One asks when will I go,
the other asks when will I bring them.
-Brother, why are you talking to yourself?
-There is no escape from you, is there sister?
Don't offend me brother. I am telling you,
I've got the solution to your problem.
-How?
-Don't you want to convince mother to let Holofira stay?
Ayse Hatun.
Give me.
Sister.
Is this how I wjll convince my mother?
With flowers and love?
Oh brother. When you can't even convince
Mother Malhun, how will you convince Holofira?
If I just convince my mother.
Sister, so you say this will work?
Rest lies in your sweet tongue brother.
You can do it, come on.
What happened Gurbuz Alp?
You were going to beat me?
You're carrying the logs, why carry me?
Don't laugh!
I carry a brother like you, over my shoulders.
-Come.
-No, no, no!
Alps, Konur Bey.
Alps.
Cumhuriyet Bavrami
I see you're having fun.
The logs were supposed to be carried.
We overdone having fun, as we are going to battle.
-With our wrestler here.
-We missed it Bey.
So you're missing battle.
Tell me..
What else does an Alp want?
To make his enemies scream with his mace.
-Allah is the Greatest!
-Anything else?
A soldier's dream is conquest.
He wants to chase that dream.
-Allah is the Greatest!
-Anything else?
A soldier wants to lie on the ground
and become martyr, before lying on his bed.
-Allah is the Greatest!
-And?
Konur Bey, they want conquest,
glory and battle.
-Allah is the Greatest!
-Praise be to the valiants of Osman Bey!
-Praise be!
-However, Konur Bey..
An Alp wants something else..
Even though he doesn't talk about it.
-Am I allowed mother?
-Come in my daughter.
-Mother?
-My Orhan?
Go, go, come on.
I swear, it is working out.
My Sultan!
I am late.
Where do you get these ideas from, Orhan Bey?
No one.
For my mother, I've made them
prepare a special feast.
-So that we can eat together.
-Praise be!
So, tell me..
Speak your mind.
What do you want from me?
Or do you want to marry?
Alright then, we will send word to
all tribes and beyliks, find you a proper bride.
Mother.
What if I'm in love with someone else?
I know what love is, my son.
However, our destiny is written for traditions.
If it was only you,
then I wouldn't have said anything.
However, you are Orhan Bey.
You also carry Osman Bey's state dream.
Yesterday, I understood again that,
that girl is not suitable for you.
After you come back from the mission,
you will take Holofira to home.
That guest has overstayed.
Mother.
-I only want time from you.
-It'll be harder for you as more time passes.
Do what I told you, Orhan Bey.
Oh my son.
I only think about your own good.
It is the command of the grand Bey, Osman Bey.
Those who join the conquest
will be given subsistence.
So that, their eagerness
for battle increases.
Thanks to Osman Bey.
As long as hearty,
real valiants stand beside him..
Osman Bey and his heritage, will live long.
Come on take it. Take it.
He liked gold before, now he likes giving it.
The right way turns people, my Bey.
What’s the matter, my Shahzade?
My brother.
-Brother!
-Did you handle it, brother?
-Thanks to Allah.
-I came back victorious.
-Praise be!
Let's go to father!
When the frontier market is opened,
...Turkmen having tough times
for long time will be at ease.
Everybody...
...is glad that the frontier market is opened, Yakup Bey.
Sons of Oghuz will be united thanks to you.
The unity will prevail forever, Karesi Bey.
There will be objecting voices. I know that.
Those who listens to objecting voices
instead of Yakup Bey's strong voice...
...will lose eventually.
Osman hesitates to pledge loyalty.
-You mean him, huh, Yakup Bey?
-Fighting to be free...
...instead of being united...
...will damage us more than
the enemy will do.
Osman is closed by his arrogance.
He will either open them or...
-Father!
-Gonca.
-Did you bring it, dear?
-I brought the firman, my bey father.
My victorious daughter.
Nobody can stand against me now.
-My Bey father.
-Welcome, son.
Thank you, my Bey. Thank you.
The map leading to the treasure, my Bey.
You accomplished the mission, huh?
-Thank you.
-Thank you, my Bey.
The location of the treasure is drawn
here step by step, my Bey.
Sultan Mesut kept the treasure that
he hid from Mongolians in these frontiers...
...not in Konya.
Around Karamese.
Under the high tree.
Around Karamese?
-Why didn't you bring it, son?
-They followed me, my Bey.
-Who?
-Gonca Hatun, Yakup Bey's daughter.
She knows I got the map.
But there is more. Gonca Hatun was there.
Sultan Mesud used his seal before he died.
How come?
Did she make a dying man use his seal?
If a lion falls, wolves take bites, Orhan Bey.
He sealed the paper to promote his sultanate.
He said he'd declare his sultanate next day.
Anyway, this treasure is what matters now.
It's the only thing to break Yakup Bey's power.
We will take it.
BismillahirRahmanirRahim.
You shouldn't protect only your lives, but also the state.
And it's Germiyanoglu Yakup Bey who Is to protect it.
You shall all pledge loyalty and stand behind him.
This is my last will for you.
This is what you've been dreaming of, my Bey.
Both the throne and power are yours now.
We did this... But is it unfair, father?
Who else but your father deserves this?
Why would it be unfair?
My good-mannered and conscientious daughter.
You think I didn't think about this?
Sometimes, for power...
...everything can be justified.
And tell me my pretty Gonca.
In these lands...
...are there anyone stronger than Germiyan?
Sstrength is what provides peace.
If I hadn't made this move, there would be a blood bath.
I know, my bey father.
But there is another matter.
-Not good, daughter?
-No, father.
Osman's son Alaaddin...
Sultan Mesud left the map of Konya treasure
to him before he died.
-Why didn't you follow him, Gonca?
-Of course I did, my bey father.
But he noticed I was following
and didn't go to the treasure.
If Osman gets the treasure,
Beys will grumble...
...questioning why Osman has the map
while you have the firman.
We will prevent this.
We'll have both the firman and the treasure.
Whatever we do, they will absolutely hit back.
For this reason, we'll be cautious. Konur.
-Go to the headquarters with Bayindir Bey.
-As you order, my Bey.
-What about the market? Yakup Bey is awaiting us.
-He will wait for me...
...but see Malhun Hatun instead.
Alaaddin, you go to the frontier market.
Keep your eyes on Yakup Bey.
I want to know about every step of his.
-As you order, my Bey.
-And you, Orhan...
-My Bey.
-You'll go for the treasure. But it's not only us who seeks it.
They will follow you.
Don't come back without the treasure.
As you order, my Bey.
Everybody get to your duties!
Mehmed!
Osman will want to capture the treasure
before I get my sultanate declared.
Keep your eyes on him!
As my Bey orders.
I will crush whoever stands in my way.
Do I have permission, my Sultan?
Come, Kanyumaz!
My Sultan, Remus got killed
while escaping from Osman's palace last night.
Good. Good.
It wouldn't be good for us if he were alive.
I knew Osman had him.
Dead or alive...
He mentioned me and what?
Could Osman beat me?
Was he able to point his sword at me?
Those who fail to shut their mouths will pass away.
Kanyumaz.
Find Cerkutay, one of Osman's alps,
and bring him to me.
As you order, my Bey.
Osman is going out.
Inform Jesus' children.
Tell them to set a trap against Osman. He should learn..
...that nowhere is safe for him.
He should know that Turks
won't be able to sleep in peace now.
-Atmaca...
-You called me, master Vasilis.
Osman will take the treasure.
You will go and inform Yakup.
The treasure is around Karamese.
That place will be turned into a bloodbath soon, Master Vasilis.
They will drown each other in that blood.
What happened, you mother's boy?
Couldn't you convince your mother?
What does that mean?
Why would I convince her?
You were the same when you were a child.
You could never lie.
But I know.
Your mother is disturbed by my presence.
Send me back to my land, Orhan.
Your mother will be happy,
I'll be happy as well.
You will get what you want.
But you have to wait for some more time.
-The roads...
-Sure. The roads...
Tell me. Why do you want me here?
Now you are playing with me Holofira.
Don't you know why?
My Shahzade. Forgive me. Alps are ready.
They are waiting for your orders.
I'm coming Dark Ali. I'm coming.
Keep running.
It is time. Come on!
-My Bey!
-Come in.
My Bey. We received news from Yenisehir's watchmen.
-What is Osman Bey doing now?
-He is building an army to walk to Lefke.
He should gain his reputation back first!
If he gains a victory,
his reputation will be glorious again.
-We knew he would go to Lefke.
-I should go and take the treasure.
-I should ruin all their opportunities.
-Stop there
We will make such a move that..
. we will turn the world into hell for him.
First, you will go to the bannerless.
You will make them obey Osman.
What is your aim, my Bey?
I prevented him from gathering Alps.
Osman will have to accept the Bannerless.
If he goes and gains a victory with bandits,
what will people say about him, Hatun?
One needs bravery to be a Bey.
But if you are going to be a Sultan...
...you must be smarter than everyone.
I am proud of you, my Bey.
We have just started, my Saadet.
I will ruin Osman's dreams about conquests.
What happened here? Are you alright?
Who did this to you?
-Alps, bring some water.
-Dumrul, come on!
Trap.
I will not leave you here.
I will not let jackals torture the innocent ones.
Showing mercy to the cruel...
...is betraying the poor.
My Bey...
What if this is Yakup Bey's game again?
No...
No... No...
They all have marks on their necks.
But they burnt them.
Apparently...
apparently they want them to infiltrate us.
From now on,
I have suspicions about everyone. -My Bey...
My Bey, Remus had the same mark on his neck.
They are all working for someone.
But who? We'll see.
Hang on... Hang on.
-Ayaz! -My Bey.
-Take her to the healing house.
-Yes my Bey.
-Hurry.
I found you unexpectedly, Mehmet Bey.
Apparently, you learned something really important.
It's obvious. Tell me, Atmaca.
I did, yes.
I learned something so important that...
...all Beys are after this.
It is worth a lot. It is a secret.
We will evaluate its worth and give you
what you deserve Atmaca. Tell me, cut it short.
-I know where Sultan Mesud's treasure is.
-Tell me. Where is it?
-The treasure is around Karamese.
-How could you get the information which we couldn't get, Atmaca?
I can smell the trophy and know
how to get it, Mehmet Bey.
Alright, Atmaca, alright.
When we take it, you will get your reward.
Thank you.
Okmen!
You will find Christian clothes right away.
-Why do you need Christian clothes?
-You will learn soon, Atmaca.
Don't forget
. The other bannerless won't know about this.
This is a secret between you and me.
Okay.
First, we will visit the Bannerless' place.
They will also have a duty.
Come on.
My Hatun, what are you doing?
I feel very well today, Kismet.
The cure Dervish Effendi
gave me made me feel very good.
It feels fine but how can you heal
if you get up so early. Take it slow.
As I'm lying in bed,
my loved ones are getting upset.
I will not lie down from now on.
-I'll get up.
-If Allah permits, my Hatun. If Allah permits.
You look so beautiful, but...
...who are you getting prepared for?
Where are you going?
Alaca?
Alaca.
What are you doing here?
Bala.
Osman.
How did this happen?
How did you get up?
-Are you all right?
-I'm all right.
I was coming for you. But you acted first.
Tell me, how did this happen?
A,Dervish Effendi prepared a cure.
I've been feeling very well lately.
-Praise be. Who is this Dervish?
-I don't know his name.
What are you doing here?
I'm so surprised
to see you up like this.
Come.
Come here. Since you are well,
let’s take a walk.
You seem quiet.
Did you have a bad dinner?
-Yakup Bey is behind Remus.
-Yakup Bey?
He tried to humiliate you in front of the Beys
and make you kiss his hand.
-What are you going to do?
-I'll do what I need to do.
I'll move towards Lefke. I have not stopped
until now and I will not stop now.
Stopping is not for you.
Don't stop. I wish I could join you as well.
You are always with me. Look.
-You are in my heart.
-Osman, you have a wound. Wait.
What's this wound? What's this?
You've been visiting our hunting ground
much recently, son of Bey.
Why?
Do you have any objection?
We'll tell you whether we have an objection or not,
if you tell us why you're here.
I've brought you a great promise.
From now on,
you will not plunder.
You'll earn more coin
than you ever imagined.
Very well, but tell us how.
What did I tell you?
I said you will obey.
And we didn't respond.
We didn't say we would obey Yakup Bey.
Not to Yakup Bey.
You will obey Osman Bey.
Why would we do that?
I told you. For coin.
You will take your coin from me.
Three chests of gold each time.
You think all these soldiers would be
down for three chests of gold only?
It's not only three chests, of course.
Osman Bey is a soldier of holy war.
When you go to war with him,
you take your share from the loot.
So you expect cattle to run away to the mountain
and you expect grass to run short,
once in a blue moon!
We want five chests of gold each time.
Alps.
Bring one more chest.
Let it be six, not five. Enjoy it.
Are you going to do what I say?
Let's say we said yes. What will you gain from it?
What do you want us to do?
What I want from you...
-My Bala...
-Osman.
I haven't left Sogut for a long time.
I want to join you.
-Of course not, you should get better.
-I'd tell you if I wasn't.
-Believe me, it will be better for me.
-My Bala.
-Don't upset me.
-It's about your health, don't do it.
I know, but I feel very well. You see.
Also I'm not saying that I'll fight.
I just want to come to the outpost and see Alps.
-I should come, right?
-All right, but you will stand behind.
-Promise me.
-I promise you, my Osman.
All right, get ready. Come on.
Kismet Hatun. Can she mount?
Thanks to the One who made us see this day.
She is all right, my Bey.
Allah, Allah.
MashaAllah.
-You are all right.
-I'm all right.
GERMIYNAOGULLARI BORDER
Everyone will surge into
this marketplace, Cerkutay.
Not only Germiyans,
all of the Turkmens will make profit.
This is what makes me happy the most.
MashaAllah, it is an unmatched marketplace.
But forgive me for my curiosity, Yakup Bey.
-Why am I here?
-I want you to...
...be my deputy in this marketplace.
Share my load.
How can I be your deputy?
Don't you see my condition?
I can see.
That's why I'm saying it.
I don't need your arms, I need your mind.
Only you can manage all those things.
Forgive me Yakup Bey,
I don't want any load other than mine.
I'm not saying to take on my load,
I'm just saying to share my load.
I know your trouble.
I like Osman Bey.
The resentment between you two
is not my problem.
Also, I’m saying the whole world
will be here, Cerkutay.
No one knows Mongols and Byzantium
better than you.
If you stay at the bazaar,
I will have nothing to worry.
I want this not for myself,
but for everyone.
I don't know if I can do this.
After everything that happened.
I don't accept anyone else as my agent,
Cerkutay.
From now on,
your word here is my word.
Lefke Headquarters
Alps!
Turahan.
What's wrong with this camp?
Alps are missing, swords are missing.
What happened here Turahan?
We agreed with all these tribes.
There used to be thousands of Alps here,
where are they?
The situation is not good, Yakup Bey..
He got all the tribes under his command.
So the tribes did not send any Alps.
We never forget the name
nor the face of those who left us behind.
We fight as we can,
but we are few, Konur Bey. What will we do?
Hold on, let me write a letter to all tribes.
There is no such thing as not keeping a promise.
The way of battle needs heart.
It is more dangerous to have non-believers beside us.
That is true, however,
how are we going to find a solution to this?
-Konur Bey, the bannerless have food.
-Let them come.
Since you came all the way here
put your life in danger, what you'll say is important.
Tell me, why are you here?
From now on, we want to get
under the banner of Osman Bey.
Behold! Cerkutay is coming!
Mother, when will Cerkutay Bey name me?
That is your father.
Don't call him 'Cerkutay Bey’.
Alright.
Come here.
What did you do, my Cerkutay?
Are we going now?
What does Yakup Bey want?
For me to stay at the bazaar.
Bazaar? You did not accept it did you?
Does that belong to us now, mother?
Guard yourselves! Cerkutay Alp is coming!
Cerkutay, don't tell me you said yes.
Look, Yakup Bey and Osman Bey is in conflict.
Do not accept it,
what will you say to Osman Bey?
There is no Osman Bey anymore, Ulgen.
From now on, this bazaar is mine.
It is ours.
My Cerkutay, Yakup Bey tries to
get Alps to his side with tricks, don't..
Who let me out of that prison?
Yakup Bey. Who made us one again?
Yakup Bey.
From now on, our place..
Is with Yakup Bey.
Shahzade Orhan came to you,
asked you to join the battle. You said no.
-Now, what happened?
-Bannerless divided into two.
Those we saw as brothers, betrayed us.
Look at that!
You were betrayed by the men you ate with.
-Why should we have you beside us.
-No.
You think we were defeated from our looks.
We are victorious.
Our goods and hunting grounds are ours.
Then what changed your mind?
-Why do you want to be beside Osman Bey?
-We want to be martyrs.
Not dying by a treacher's knife.
Because of that Atmaca dog,
there is no caravans to hit.
If this goes like this,
we won't make it this winter.
Why don't you say this from the start.
So you want to stand beside us for coin.
Then, those who pay you,
can restrain all of you.
We do not need coin lovers.
We need those that stand beside what we believe.
We can't see through you anyways.
Osman Bey will decide, go wait there.
The sign on the map shows here.
Search around.
We search for a sign of arrow, look sharp.
Alps!
Come on.
Atmaca. We won't let him get the treasure.
Treasure belongs to those who want it.
We will give our lives, but not the treasure.
There you are. Get the cart.
e don't know what waits us inside.
Everyone will look sharp.
Alps, you will stay guard at the entrance.
Bring the torch.
-Now is the time.
-Stop, let them go in.
Be careful, come on.
Is that Alaeddin
-Yes, mother.
-What is this Alaeddin like?
As clever as to not to be taken lightly.
Gonca, you are the one saying this?
I couldn't get the map as I took him lightly.
I've tried to trick him many times.
-But he left an empty paper instead of the map.
-You got really angry about this I see.
Don't worry,
I won't let them have the treasure.
I don't worry, father. As you know,
I never forget what was done to me.
-I will not let that go unpunished.
-I know, come on.
Let me see his wit too.
Let's see if he is like you said.
-Welcome, Malhun Hatun.
-Thank you, Yakup Bey.
Cerkutay?
-So, where is Osman Bey?
-He has an important task.
There is no greater task than
to meet in this bazaar, where unites every state.
If there was, we would've done it.
-He will come here as soon as possible.
-Good. Good.
Alaaddin Bey, let's go.
I appreciate your efforts, Saadet Hatun.
The market looks magnificent.
It will be even better
when the trade starts.
Malhun Hatun,
this is your stall.
It seems you love Kayi rugs, Saadet Hatun.
You keep talking about them.
-This is the stall that you think our rugs deserve, huh?
-It's nook or cranny.
-Malhun Hatun, don't you like it?
-Well...
The value of a stall is measured
by its goods not by where it is.
When the goods I got prepared
in Yenisehir arrive, you will know...
...what I mean, Saadet Hatun.
Come here, hatuns.
Meet her. UIgen.
Oh... You already know her, Malhun Hatun.
This way.
In the name of Allah, the merciful, the compassionate.
Gokmen, shoot arrows.
They are after Orhan.
Let's go. We shouldn't lose them.
Orhan, where are you?
Orhan! Orhan! Orhan where are you?
-Take this.
-Thank you.
-Are you a doctor now, Scholar?
-I'm a doctor for those looking for heal, Trickster Hatun.
Watch your words!
When did you even see me doing tricks?
What? You aren't embarrassed while doing tricks
but you are when you're called so?
You always hang out with your mother and sister.
And your brother walks with your father, huh?
Look who is talking! Weren't you supposed to be
preparing silk dowry with your mother in your tent?
-Gonca Hatun, daisy is good for nerves.
You apparently need it.
-Scholar!
-Gonca Hatun.
-Saadet Hatun is awaiting you.
-We aren't done yet, Scholar!
I'm always here, Trickster Hatun.
-My Bey.
-What's the situation?
-Yakup Bey gave an order to tribe beys.
-And?
"Don't provide alps for Osman Bey", he said.
Okay.
When the wolf makes a decision,
...he knows the hunter and the awaiting pain.
No problem.
-Why are The Bannerless here?
-It seems Shahzade's plan worked.
They want to pledge loyalty. They say they want to
fight for Islam and seek no haram anymore.
-But I can send them away.
-I want no pledges!
Go to Yakup Bey! Come on!
Osman Bey! Osman Bey!
We are skillful in the battlefield.
Do no turn us down, Osman Bey.
Germiyanogullari Border
Trading is a blessing.
Blessings come from Allah.
This marketplace, which will make us all happy,
will be open tomorrow, with Allah's permission.
Tribes and cities will bring their goods
to this marketplace and sell them.
Goods will come not only from us,
but also from the east, the west...
...and the land of Persians.
-May it be blessed for all of us!
-Aamen!
Now you are wondering,
who will be in charge of this marketplace?
My valiant, Cerkutay Bey, come here.
He is responsible for this market and he is in control.
A Bey, who has endured all these
years of captivity, will manage this market well.
-Isn't that right, Alaeddin Bey?
-Sure.
You can't find anyone better than
Cerkutay Bey, Yakup Bey.
Congratulations, Cerkutay Bey.
Thanks to Yakup Bey..
He deemed me worthy of this position.
I swear... Sleeping is haram for me until I make
this marketplace the biggest marketplace in the world.
This marketplace is offering us wealth.
And I, with Allah's consent, will achieve this.
And this must be known.
-Send my greetings to Osman Bey, Alaeddin Bey.
-Alaykum Salaam, Yakup Bey.
Cerkutay Bey.
My Shahzade. Yakup Bey
and Beys are leaving on their horses.
We will go after them. Come on.
So you are talented, huh?
Why are you testing Orhan Bey?
Why?
Men do not fight behind a man who is not stronger
than them, Osman Bey. We wanted to see it.
And a man who is weaker than him doesn't
want their accompany!
Now I will test you.
You will face me now. To the field!
The body cannot carry the heart, It is always apart,
Do not stop, the Bannerless! Yell with all your clout!
Say something if you cannot defeat your opponent,
Call your companion... -Hit, hit!
We will part our ways. We will look everywhere.
We will check all the trees! Everywhere! Come on!
The treasure... The treasure is here.
Thanks to You, my Allah. Alps, come here!
-Orhan!
-The treasure...
...the treasure is under this rock.
We will dig here.
-Orhan! Orhan!
-Holofira? Holofira!
-What are you doing here?
-They are after you! -Who?
-Allah is the Greatest!
-The treasure is ours!
-What are you doing here?
-Why do you care, Orhan?
Do not take another step, Scholar.
The next arrow will find your heart.
Get down.
-Trickster Hatun.
-Come on! I said get down!
Tell me... Why are you chasing my horse?
I am on my way. But you never stop
following me, Trickster Hatun.
I asked you a question.
I said, why are you following my horse?
And I asked you.
Why do you keep following me?
Your eyes are always on me.
-Did you...
-Did I what?
Did you fall in love with me?
-They are talented, my Bey.
-And they are brave.
One needs to be brave to fight Osman Bey.
This time, you will come and fight with us.
But you won't take a piece from the trophy.
Let's see if you are really doing that
for the holy cause.
If you play a game,
this will bring your end.
Alps! Everyone will support each other!
We are going to Lefke! Come on!
-Do you trust them?
-No. Those who want gold can do anything for gold.
But if we rejected them,
they would talk behind our backs. Therefore...
...there is no need to offend our veterans.
-You are right. We will keep them in sight.
My Bala... Come on. Forget about that.
Tell me now... Did your sword become rusty?
When did the swords of Sisters become rusty, my Osman?
My Shahzade! Protect the Shahzade! Alps!
My Shahzade!
-Protect the Shahzade!
-Orhan!
Orhan!
Orhan, we need to go!
stand up, come on! -My Alps...
Come with me!
Orhan, they are crowded! I said come on!
Alps! Alps, we are going back!
Go to Karayazi region. We will meet there!
Holofira, my Alps!
Come with me! They are too crowded!
We are going back, Alps!
Go after them! Don't let them run away!
Will we follow them, my Shahzade?
The Bannerless will descend on them like vultures.
We will take the treasure, Okmen.
Sultan Mesud's treasure belongs to Germiyan.
Come. Come.
Are you alright?
Holofira!
Come with me... Let's go.
Come on.
The trail goes this way. Come on!
Come... Come.
Orhan!
Come on.
Are you alright?
Orhan...
-Holofira...
-We will get out of this place.
Bey's son...
Dervish..
Dervish Efendi..
Orhan... I will find you Orhan.
Germiyanogullari Border
MashaAllah.
Kayi's carpets have been brought.
MashaAllah, they.are so beautiful
Of course, UIgen. Kayi's Hatuns weave the best carpets...
...in the Frontiers.
Saadet Hatun, if you like any of them,
let us give it as a gift.
Come on UIgen.
Pick the most beautiful one.
Show your skills.
Alps, give me a hand.
Your first sale is from us and
the grace Is from Allah.
UIgen, have the carpet ready.
Do you want me to put the carpets in the tent,
Saadet Hatun?
Lay it here.
Come on, lay it out.
Fitnat.
Inform Atmaca.
Malhun Hatun's caravan will not join
the marketplace tomorrow.
You need to put the one who's out of her limits in her place,
so that she cannot lay eyes on your post.
Let's see what she's going to do when
she's ruined and her bench is empty tomorrow.
I'll show you how to be great, Malhun.
She is straight-forwardly insulting us.
Are we going to let her get away with it, mother?
We will not, of course.
I know what to do to the one...
...who puts mud on Kayi's efforts.
What's that?
What are these banners?
Yakup Bey.
Holofira. Give me the sword.
Give me the sword.
In the name of Allah,
the merciful, the compassionate.
Thank you Dervish Effendi.
You came here like Khidr.
Don't even mention it.
One escapes everything...
...but cannot escapes his destiny.
Ya Shafi (The One Who cures).
When and where
we will be is predetermined.
The test is also predetermined.
-And questions as well.
-Thank you.
The test is determined.
And questions.
That's right, but the important thing is,
one should not forget that he's being tested.
And that test is intertwined.
You are tested with justice.
You are tested with position.
You are tested with money.
You are tested with love.
You either pass the test and move on,
or you lose your mind along with the test
and turn into a mad man.
Since Haqq made us cross paths,
do you want me to give you a secret?
We do.
I mean, I do.
Please, Dervish Effendi.
This sword
that caused this wound and cauterized it,
just as it is an object,
love is also an object.
And it is such an object that it is too precious to touch.
Neither steel, nor copper,
nor silver, nor gold, nor emeralds, nor rubies.
There's nothing as precious as love.
Love is like a sun.
One without love has a heart similar a rock.
What does heart have to do with stone?
Just as the sun warms the earth
and illuminates the darkness,
so is love.
Makes you experienced.
Boils your blood.
Makes you generous.
Is there a single fruit that doesn't get sunlight?
They die if they don't.
There is no such being that doesn't
get love as well. If they don't, they die.
Since the most precious thing is love..
Then, the hardest task is..
The one you have with it.
Son of Bey.
Now you say, why did you tell me this, Dervish?
The hearts without love, hearts of stone..
They do not give anything
but unrest in this world, that's why.
Now, I tell you this..
So that we stay with love,
we become one of lovers.
The owner of love is no one but Allah.
So that no matter where we look,
we look with the goodwill of Allah.
As only those who look with the goodwill of Allah
can give peace and serenity to this world.
May Allah..
-Allow us to be one of those.
-Aameen.
Make way!
The Sultan of all states, Yakup Bey.
Welcome to Germiyan lands, Osman Bey.
Thank you.
Congrats on your conquest, Yakup Bey.
It was great already.
My dear friend Yakup Bey.
You were of great help to me. Welcome.
Thank youi, Lord Zenon.
-To what do I owe this crowded visit?
-What's the matter?
You don't have the power to feed us all?
Of course, if you are a guest.
Lefka has rich soil.
We know.
However, we do not like being guests.
We own every place we place our foot on.
-Soldiers!
-Ya Allah!
Your home, Lord Zenon, is mine now.
- Allah is the greatest!
Alps, take over the castle.
First..
He imprisoned..
my valiant Cerkutay.
I took vengeance.
Then, he imprisoned the mightiest of my Beys..
Osman Bey.
I took vengeance.
I took out all of them, with Allah's permission.
The way of battle, is the way of all, Osman Bey.
As this fits..
To the Sultan of the State.
However..
You took pillagers beside you,
on your way to Lefka.
Your battle is not holy.
Nor conquest.
But to pillage. Right, Beys?
-Kanyumaz!
-My Sultan.
In the name of Allah, the merciful,
the compassionate.
Trust is not only for the heart,
but for the state as well.
And that is, given to Germiyan..
Yakup Bey.
All of you will kneel to Yakup Bey..
And stand beside him.
And that is my final will to you.
You neither look like grand vizier..
Nor Mother Sultan.
That is correct.
Because none of them were Sultan.
contact us: turkision@gmail.com